pacyber.org 2014-06-25

# PA Cyber | The Pennsylvania Cyber Charter School - Privacy Policy

#### WHAT THIS POLICY COVERS

The Pennsylvania Cyber Charter School (PA Cyber) is committed to respecting the privacy of visitors to this site, as well as respecting the privacy of those individuals utilizing our services. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to let you know how we collect and use information that we may gather from you on this website. This policy applies to all sites on the PA Cyber domain (pacyber.org), and discloses how we collect, use, share, and protect information gathered about you on our sites or systems.

This policy does not apply to the practices of organizations that PA Cyber does not control or to people who PA Cyber does not employ or manage.

#### WHAT AND HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

We collect information when you visit our site and voluntarily enter and submit information on our online form requesting to opt-in and be placed on our email distribution list and/or receive a phone call from us to deliver additional information to you. When requesting service on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, address, telephone number, and email address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Information collected also includes items such as domain name, time spent on our site, browser information, connection speed, and whether you are a new visitor to the site. Additionally, items related to how visitors navigate to our site are collected including search engine and keyword information. All of this information helps us analyze trends to determine how to best serve our users and how we can continually improve our service.

The PA Cyber Online Store is operated by a third party that may collect personal information in order to ship goods that are purchased by online visitors. A link is supplied to their website (http://www.companycasuals.com/pacyber/start.jsp). Information collected on that Site is covered under that site’s own privacy policy as it is not under the control of PA Cyber.

#### COOKIES

A "cookie" is a file placed on your personal computer's hard drive by a website that allows it to monitor an individual’s use of the site. PA Cyber currently does not use cookies for tracking and use purposes.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION PROTECTION

The privacy and confidential nature of personally identifiable information that PA Cyber may obtain concerning its students, employees, alumni and other individuals is of utmost importance to PA Cyber. PA Cyber will only disclose personally identifiable information on a strict need-to-know basis and to the extent required or permitted by law. PA Cyber maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to minimize the risk of unauthorized access or disclosure of this information. For instance, PA Cyber utilizes industry standard protocols such as SSL encryption to secure confidential information. All student data will be accessed only by those PA Cyber personnel that require information access as part of their responsibility. Employee credentials are required to gain access to such data.   

Moreover, all student-centric systems are restricted by school-issued student credentials. All PA Cyber student data is held locally, and is controlled by the school. While PA Cyber does employ resources from third parties, all products are hosted and controlled locally.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe information at the bottom of each email.

#### YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF OUR PRIVACY PRACTICES

By using this site you accept PA Cyber’s Privacy Policy and the conditions posted on our site. PA Cyber reserves the right to update, change, modify, or remove portions of this policy at any time.  

#### CONTACTING US

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us here.
